I'm Andy Sealshaw for the record and we are on the record with Kwame.
Now you mentioned that your father is no longer with us. What is a song that reminds you of your
father? Love Supreme, John Coltrane. Oh, jazz. We spent a lot of time listening to jazz. My
father had a huge jazz collection, very rare jazz records. And when I was a little kid, like nine,
I had an understanding of what scratching was. But I thought scratching was taking an actual needle
and scratching the hell out of a record. So I took like, he has this, this, this group,
the modern jazz quartet, John Coltrane, Sun Ra, and I took his, some of his precious records.
Oh no. And then I played them and I'm listening. I'm rocking.
If you hit the turntable, it would make this noise like, boom, like an 808. So the records
and I hit it, boom. I'm like rocking. And my father walks in, what the hell? And I'm like,
I'm scratching. And he's like, what? I'm scratching. He's like, no. And instead of destroying me,
he took me directly to this kid. He knew who was a DJ. Show him how to scratch. That's my father.
Oh, wow. That's, that's so fortunate that you got to have a dad like that. That's what's up.
Rest in peace.